{"id": "NER-001", "text": "The 3rd Battalion, Singapore Guards conducted Exercise WALLABY 2025 at Shoalwater Bay Training Area in Queensland, Australia, from 15 SEP to 12 OCT 2025. The battalion deployed with BIONIX II infantry fighting vehicles and integrated with elements from the Australian 7th Brigade.", "entities": [{"text": "3rd Battalion, Singapore Guards", "type": "military-unit", "start": 4, "end": 35}, {"text": "Exercise WALLABY 2025", "type": "operation-name", "start": 46, "end": 67}, {"text": "Shoalwater Bay Training Area", "type": "location", "start": 71, "end": 100}, {"text": "Queensland, Australia", "type": "location", "start": 104, "end": 125}, {"text": "BIONIX II", "type": "weapon-system", "start": 180, "end": 189}, {"text": "Australian 7th Brigade", "type": "military-unit", "start": 233, "end": 255}]}
{"id": "NER-002", "text": "CONFIDENTIAL//REL TO SGP, AUS — BGen Tan Wei Ming, Commander 9th Division, authorized the deployment of AGM-84L Harpoon Block II anti-ship missiles to RSS Formidable (68) during maritime patrol operations in the South China Sea, effective 091630ZAPR2026.", "entities": [{"text": "CONFIDENTIAL//REL TO SGP, AUS", "type": "classification-level", "start": 0, "end": 30}, {"text": "BGen Tan Wei Ming", "type": "person", "start": 33, "end": 50}, {"text": "9th Division", "type": "military-unit", "start": 63, "end": 75}, {"text": "AGM-84L Harpoon Block II", "type": "weapon-system", "start": 107, "end": 131}, {"text": "RSS Formidable", "type": "military-unit", "start": 157, "end": 171}, {"text": "South China Sea", "type": "location", "start": 211, "end": 226}, {"text": "091630ZAPR2026", "type": "date-time-group", "start": 238, "end": 252}]}
{"id": "NER-003", "text": "The Defence Science and Technology Agency awarded a SGD 120M contract to ST Engineering for the next-generation Protected Combat Support Vehicle under Project BELLEROPHON. Delivery is expected to the 1st Commando Battalion by Q3 2027.", "entities": [{"text": "Defence Science and Technology Agency", "type": "organization", "start": 4, "end": 41}, {"text": "ST Engineering", "type": "organization", "start": 72, "end": 86}, {"text": "Protected Combat Support Vehicle", "type": "weapon-system", "start": 107, "end": 139}, {"text": "Project BELLEROPHON", "type": "operation-name", "start": 146, "end": 165}, {"text": "1st Commando Battalion", "type": "military-unit", "start": 195, "end": 217}]}
{"id": "NER-004", "text": "SECRET//NOFORN — COL Priya Nair, Director of Military Intelligence, briefed RADM David Koh on Operation TRIDENT LANCE intercept results. Analysis indicates PLA Navy Type 055 destroyer Nanchang (101) conducted electronic warfare emissions collection within 45nm of Pedra Branca on 221430ZMAR2026.", "entities": [{"text": "SECRET//NOFORN", "type": "classification-level", "start": 0, "end": 14}, {"text": "COL Priya Nair", "type": "person", "start": 17, "end": 31}, {"text": "RADM David Koh", "type": "person", "start": 68, "end": 82}, {"text": "Operation TRIDENT LANCE", "type": "operation-name", "start": 86, "end": 109}, {"text": "PLA Navy", "type": "organization", "start": 142, "end": 150}, {"text": "Type 055 destroyer", "type": "weapon-system", "start": 151, "end": 169}, {"text": "Nanchang", "type": "military-unit", "start": 170, "end": 178}, {"text": "Pedra Branca", "type": "location", "start": 239, "end": 251}, {"text": "221430ZMAR2026", "type": "date-time-group", "start": 255, "end": 269}]}
{"id": "NER-005", "text": "The Republic of Singapore Air Force 145 Squadron scrambled two F-15SG Strike Eagles from Paya Lebar Air Base in response to an unidentified aircraft approaching the Singapore Flight Information Region. RSAF personnel coordinated with the Malaysian Armed Forces 3rd Air Division throughout the incident.", "entities": [{"text": "Republic of Singapore Air Force", "type": "organization", "start": 4, "end": 35}, {"text": "145 Squadron", "type": "military-unit", "start": 36, "end": 48}, {"text": "F-15SG Strike Eagle", "type": "weapon-system", "start": 63, "end": 82}, {"text": "Paya Lebar Air Base", "type": "location", "start": 89, "end": 108}, {"text": "Singapore Flight Information Region", "type": "location", "start": 158, "end": 193}, {"text": "RSAF", "type": "organization", "start": 195, "end": 199}, {"text": "Malaysian Armed Forces", "type": "organization", "start": 226, "end": 248}, {"text": "3rd Air Division", "type": "military-unit", "start": 249, "end": 265}]}
